William Kneeland

15 Years of video game experience, both in playing games casually and competitively, fixing bugs in games and game engines, making maps and other content for games, creating games from engines and testing games for bugs and other issues. 1 year of customer satisfaction experience. Possesses expertise in Java, HTML and CSS.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BRICK CITY CATERING, Rochester, NY

Catering Waitstaff, August 2017 - Present

- Take care of the food/make sure it is not left out for longer than 2 hours
- Show food to the customers and recommend different foods
- Bring food back and forth from the kitchen
- Make sure food looks presentable at all times
- Make sure that food is not given to someone if they are allergic to it
- Be ready to answer questions from customers at any time, or be able to find someone who can answer. NEVER ANSWER A QUESTION IF I DO NOT 100% KNOW THE ANSWER

SCHMOOSES BAR & GRILL, Jackman, ME

Dish Washer & Bus Boy, August 2015 - August 2016

- Washed all the dishes used from 6pm to whenever the night slowed down
- Made salads or desserts if things were too busy for the sous-chef to keep up
- Bused tables when things were too busy for the waitresses to do it
- Brought up food supplies from the freezer if the kitchen was running low
- Cleaned the kitchen if there wasn't anything left to do, or if the night was slow

To start, I was very slow with washing the dishes, but over time I became much better at it and my boss and other employees were very happy with my ability to wash the dishes and the speed at which I could wash at.

EDUCATION

ROCHESTER INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, Rochester, NY

Major in Web and Mobile Computing, August 2017 - Present

• Still attending as a full time student

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Adequate at playing guitar
- Skilled at coding with Java
- Skilled at coding with HTML and CSS
- Skilled at planning ahead
- Skilled with Hammer map maker
- Beginner knowledge of how to use Unreal Engine 4